Sarcasm and jazz have something surprisingly in common: You know them when you hear them.
讽刺和爵士乐有一个出人意料的共同点：你一听就能认出它们。
Sarcasm is mostly understood through tone of voice, which is used to portray the opposite of the literal words.
讽刺主要通过语气来理解，这种语气用来表现与字面意思相反的含义。
For example, when someone says, “Well, that’s exactly what I need right now,” their tone can tell you it’s not what they need at all.
例如，有人说“嗯，这正是我现在需要的”时，他的语气能让你听出，这根本不是他需要的。
Most frequently, sarcasm highlights an irritation or is, quite simply, mean.
最常见的情况是，讽刺要么是在点出某件令人恼火的事，要么说白了，就是刻薄。
If you want to be happier and improve your relationships, cut out sarcasm.
如果你想更快乐、改善人际关系，那就戒掉讽刺吧。
Why?
为什么？
Because sarcasm is actually hostility disguised as humor.
因为讽刺其实是伪装成幽默的敌意。
Despite smiling outwardly, many people who receive sarcastic comments feel put down and often think the sarcastic person is rude, or contemptible.
许多人听到讽刺自己的话时，尽管表面上笑着，心里却觉得受到了贬低，而且常常认为说这些讽刺话的人粗鲁无礼，或者令人鄙视。
Indeed, it’s not surprising that the word sarcasm derives from the Greek word “sarkazein,” which literally means “to tear or strip the flesh off.”
的确，sarcasm（讽刺）一词源于希腊语单词“sarkazein”，而后者的字面意思是“撕下或剥下皮肉”，这也就不足为奇了。
Hence, it’s no wonder that sarcasm is often preceded by the word “cutting” and that it hurts.
因此，难怪sarcasm（讽刺）前面常常冠以“cutting”（尖刻的）一词，也难怪讽刺会伤人。
What’s more, since actions strongly determine thoughts and feelings, when a person consistently acts sarcastically, it may only serve to heighten their underlying hostility and insecurity.
此外，由于行为在很大程度上决定着思想和情感，一个人如果一贯以讽刺的方式行事，可能只会加剧其潜在的敌意和不安全感。
After all, when you come right down to it, sarcasm can be used as a subtle form of bullying—and most bullies are angry, insecure, or cowardly.
毕竟，归根结底，讽刺可以用作一种隐蔽的欺凌方式，而大多数欺凌者都心怀愤怒、缺乏安全感或者懦弱。
Alternatively, when a person stops voicing negative comments, especially sarcastic ones, they may soon start to feel happier and more self-confident.
反过来，一个人如果不再说负面的话，尤其是讽刺的话，可能很快就会开始感到更快乐、更自信。
Also, other people in their life benefit even more because they no longer have to hear the emotionally hurtful language of sarcasm.
而且，这个人身边的其他人受益还要更大，因为他们不必再听那些伤人感情的讽刺话语了。
Now, I’m not saying all sarcasm is bad.
话说回来，我并不是说所有讽刺都不好。
It may just be better used sparingly—like a potent spice in cooking.
只不过，讽刺或许还是少用为好，就像烹饪时味道浓烈的香料一样。
Too much of the spice, and the dish will be overwhelmed by it.
这种香料放得太多，就会盖过菜本身的味道。
Similarly, an occasional dash of sarcastic wit can spice up a chat and add an element of humor to it.
同样，偶尔来一点讽刺式的机智，能给聊天调调味，增添几分幽默。
But a big or steady serving of sarcasm will overwhelm the emotional flavor of any conversation and can taste very bitter to its recipient.
但是，大份的或接连不断的讽刺会盖过任何谈话的情感味道，而且对被讽刺的人来说，尝起来可能会非常苦涩。
So, tone down the sarcasm and work on clever wit instead, which is usually without any hostility and thus more appreciated by those you’re communicating with.
所以，收敛一下讽刺，转而在巧妙的机智上下功夫吧；机智通常不带任何敌意，因此更受与你交流的人欣赏。
In essence, sarcasm is easy, while true, harmless wit takes talent.
从本质上说，讽刺很容易，而真正的、无害的机智则需要才华。
Thus, the main difference between wit and sarcasm is that, as already stated, sarcasm is often hostility disguised as humor.
因此，机智与讽刺的主要区别在于，如前所述，讽刺往往是伪装成幽默的敌意。
It can be intended to hurt and is often bitter and biting.
讽刺可能意在伤人，而且往往尖酸刻薄。
Witty statements are usually in response to someone’s unhelpful remarks or behaviors, and the intent is to untangle and clarify the issue by emphasizing its absurdities.
机智的话语通常是在回应某人无益的言论或行为，用意是通过强调其中的荒谬之处，来理清和阐明问题。
Sarcastic statements are expressed in a cutting manner; witty remarks are delivered with undisguised and harmless humor.
讽刺的话语以尖刻的方式表达出来；机智的话则带着不加掩饰、无害的幽默说出来。